palet.ly 2012-12-13

# Like a look? Make it yours!

**We encourage you to go through our Privacy Policy to gain complete understanding of how Paletly and its associated websites manage your personal data.**

Paletly is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy tells you about our online collection and use of data. The terms of this policy apply to all Paletly websites, unless different terms are specified in a form or contract provided to you online or offline.

By using this site, you understand and agree to the terms of this policy. This site is owned by Paletly and may be accessed via the internet. For data protection purposes, Paletly is the controller and, unless otherwise noted, is also the processor of data. Information collected may be retained, and may be stored, processed, accessed, and used in jurisdictions whose privacy laws may be different and less protective than those of your home jurisdiction.

**COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
When you visit this site, certain kinds of information, such as the website that referred you to us, your IP address, browser type and language, and access times, may be collected automatically as part of the site's operation. We also may collect navigational information, including information about the pages you view, the links you click, content you download and any/all other actions taken in connection with and during your visit to the web site.

We may combine your visit and navigational information with personal information that you provide. You may always choose not to provide personal information, but if you so choose, certain products and services may not be available to you. Personal information (e.g., your username and password, your name, your mailing address, email address, and phone number) is collected when you register. Additional personal information (e.g., your credit card number and billing address) is collected to process transactions or to provide you with products and services.

Demographic information (e.g., your age, hobbies, qualifications, profession, working life, choices, income, gender, or interests) may also be collected and may be linked to your personal information.

**USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
Paletly collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve our sites, to process your transactions, to provide customer service, to perform research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies, to do all these on behalf of our clients and to display content that is customized to your interests and preferences.

We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send transaction-related communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders, and purchase confirmations. We may also send you surveys or marketing communications to inform you of new products or services or other information that may be of interest. If you do not wish to receive marketing communications, you may follow the "unsubscribe" instructions included within each email communication. Please keep in mind that, if you choose not to receive marketing communications, you will continue to receive transactional or account communications (e.g., confirmation emails and account balance statements). The information and data provided by you at times may be shared extensively in various formats and forms, with other users and third parties (individuals, corporate, NGOs, organizations, institutions, clients, general public) at the sole discretion of Paletly.

Personal information collected by Paletly may be stored and processed in India or in any other country in which Paletly or its affiliates, subsidiaries, contractors or agents, so wish or maintain facilities, and by using our sites or services, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country/region.

**SHARING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We may share your personal information within our corporate group, including with our subsidiaries and divisions, all of whom may use your information for the purposes disclosed herein.

We may share your personal information with service providers who perform services on our behalf. For example, we may hire other companies to handle the processing of payments, to provide data storage, to host websites, to fulfill orders and shipments, to assist in direct marketing, to conduct audits, etc. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to provide the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

Information about our customers, including personal information, may be disclosed as part of any merger, acquisition, or sale of the company and/or its assets, as well as in the unlikely event of insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, in which personal information would be transferred as one of the business assets of the company. We will notify you of such an occurrence as described in the "Changes to This Privacy Policy" section below.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or protect the rights, property or safety of our company, employees, customers, or the public.

**ACCESSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
If you would like to review or revise information that you previously provided to us, you may access your information in the "My Account" section of the website. If you need additional assistance, please contact us at privacy@palet.ly. Please be advised that you cannot change your username without re-registering.

**USE OF COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES**  
Paletly uses "cookies" to enable you to sign in to our services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard drive. Cookies contain information, including personal information that can later be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. The information that cookies collect includes the date and time of your visit, your registration information, and your navigational and purchase history.

Cookies offer you many conveniences. They allow us to identify registered users when they return to the site so that they can retrieve previous image search results, access Lightboxes and view their previous activity. Cookies also save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information.

In some cases, our third-party service providers may use cookies on our sites. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Paletly only, and does not cover the use of cookies by third parties.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of our sites and services that depend on cookies.

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies, including single-pixel gifs (also known as web beacons) on our websites and in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters. These tiny electronic images assist us in determining how many users have visited certain pages or opened messages or newsletters. We do not use these images to collect personal information.

**SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to help protect your personal information. For instance, when you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology. No method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If a password is used to protect your account and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential.

**FORUMS, BLOGS & OTHER INTERACTIVE SERVICES**  
Our websites may include discussion forums or other interactive areas or services, including blogs, chat rooms, bulletin boards, message boards, online hosting or storage services, or other areas or services in which you or third parties create, post or store any content, messages, comments, materials or other items on the sites ("Interactive Areas"). If you use an Interactive Area, you should be aware that these areas are open to the public and any personal information you post or provide at registration may be viewable by others. We are not responsible for personal information you submit in connection with the Interactive Areas, nor are we responsible for how others might use that information, including sending you unsolicited messages. Interactive Area postings may be retained indefinitely. If at any time you would like to remove a posting, please email us at privacy@Palet.ly. Removal of a posting from an Interactive Area does not mean that the posting will be deleted from our systems.

**EMAIL REFERRALS**  
If you choose to use our email referral services to tell a friend about our products or services (including images in your Lightbox, promotional campaigns, new websites, job postings, etc.), we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will use that information to send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site and review the product or service you have selected. We may use a third-party provider to administer this function, but any such third party provider may only use the information submitted to facilitate this one-time email.

**CHILDREN & AGE LIMIT**  
We do not intend to solicit or collect personal information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are under 18, you should not use or enter information on this site, including without limitation, any Interactive Areas of the site.

**LINKS**  
We may link to websites, including those of our third-party content providers that have different privacy policies and practices from those disclosed here. We assume no responsibility for the policies or practices of such linked sites, and encourage you to become acquainted with them prior to use.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**  
We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy at any time. When we make changes, we will revise the "last updated" date at the top of the policy. You are expected to update yourself and we encourage you to review this policy whenever/every time you visit one of our sites.

**CONTACT INFORMATION**  
For any other information, you can contact Paletly by emailing us at privacy@palet.ly.
